Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとう
Your smile is wonderful.
笑顔が素敵だな
Looks erotic.
エロそうな
Is it erotic?
エロいですか?
It might be erotic.
エロいかもしれない
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなんですか
That's nice, smile.
いいですね、笑顔
How old are you now?
今は何歳ですか?
I'm 19 years old now.
今は19歳
It's red.
赤いですね
What are you doing?
何してる?
Usually.
普段は
I usually go to university and major in science.
普段は大学で、理系
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
I'm in science.
理系なんだ
What are you studying?
何を勉強してるの?
Medicine.
薬や
medicine?
薬?
Making medicine.
薬品づくり
That's right.
そうなんだ
You're smart.
頭いいんだね
Your smile is wonderful.
笑顔が素敵だね
I've just started my first year at university.
大学1年生入ったばっかりだな
Is it fun?
楽しいですか?
It's fun.
楽しいです
What's important?
何が大事なの?
Talking with friends, what else?
友達と喋ったりとか、 あとは何だろう
Going out to eat after university, going to business on a break, etc.
大学終わりにご飯行ったりとか、 休憩日にビジネに行ったり
Or something.
とか
That's great.
最 高だね
It's fun.
楽しいですね
Since it's a science major, there must be a lot of boys at school, right?
理系だから、学校は男の子が多いんじゃない?
I agree.
そうですね
Lots of boys too.
男の子も結構
Isn't he really popular?
めっちゃモテでしょ?
Very popular.
たくさんモテ
Do you feel like you can't deny that?
そこは否定せずみたいな感じ?
yes.
はい
If such a cute child were at school, everyone would not be able to stop playing wooden tools.
こんな可愛い子が学校にいたら、 みんな木器が止まらなくなるん
Isn't it?
じゃない?
It might be dangerous.
や ばいかもしれない
Woodenware hasn't stopped, right?
木器止まってないでしょ?
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏はいるの?
I don't have a boyfriend, that's right.
彼氏はいなくて、 そうなんだ
How many people have you dated so far?
今まで何人くらいと付き合いしたことは?
3 people.
3人
Do you have physical contact with everyone?
全員と体のお付き合い?
I agree.
そうですね
3 people.
3人
How was it?
どう でした?
yes.
はい
About 3 people with experience?
経験人数3人くらい?
I agree.
そうですね
Do you do anything else?
それ以外はしない?
With my boyfriend.
彼氏と
I see.
そうか
How long ago was the last match?
最後に一致したのはどのくらい前ですか?
About 2 or 3 months ago.
2、3ヶ月前くらい
The person you were dating?
その付き合ってた人と?
Was that good?
それは良かった?
it was good.
良かった
it was good?
良かった?
You seem to like the edge.
エッジ好きそうだね
I like it.
好きです
Is that so?
そうなの?
I haven't been feeling horny lately.
最近ムラムラというか、 してないんですよ
Yeah, I haven't.
うん、してない
Isn't your ass sexy?
ケツがエロいんでしょ?
that's right.
そうです
My waist.
腰が
I'm curious though.
気になるんだけど
My waist?
腰が?
The angle of her waist seems erotic.
腰が、角度がエロいらしいです
Come on, Kunet.
こう、くねっと
Yeah?
ええ?
That's what I said too.
そういうのも言ってたから
be on one's mind.
気 になる
Your ass is so erotic.
ケツがエロいな
The back is erotic.
バックがエロい
It seems like it could work in any company.
どこの会社にも入れそうです
I wish I had said that in the interview.
面接でそれ言ったらさ
My waist is erotic.
腰がエロいですって
Any big company would be able to get into it.
どんな大企業でも入れそうじゃん
I'll hire you.
俺、採用しちゃうよ
I see.
そうか
A few different things.
ちょっと 色々ね
I think it's embarrassing though.
恥ずかしいと思いますけど
I'll take a look.
見 ちゃいます
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張してます
Have you ever had sex with your ex-boyfriend?
元彼とハメ撮りみたいなしたことは?
Oh, no.
あ、ないです
do not have?
ない?
Isn't there?
ないか
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
first time.
初めて
first time?
初めて?
amazing.
すごい
huge.
でかい
It might also be a technique.
技法でもあるかも
That's right.
そうだよね
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えた
Have you been rubbed?
揉まれてきた?
揉まれてきたの?
yes.
はい
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
Ah, but that's fine.
あ、でもいいね
I'll rub you all the time,
ずっと揉んじゃうね、
this.
これ
Ah, it comes out quite a bit.
あ、 結構出るね
Isn't your tongue long?
舌長くない?
I have a long tongue.
舌長いんですよ
It's long, isn't it?
長いよね
amazing.
すごい
long.
長い
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
It's huge.
でかいね
It's long and feels really good.
長くてめっちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいわ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
God's.
神の
It's God's tongue.
神の舌だもん
Erotic.
エロ
Your body is white.
白いね、体
Half undressed.
半脱ぎ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You're wearing a naughty tongue.
エッチな舌着してるね
Purple.
紫
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃうか、じゃあ
Clothes.
お洋服
Okay, then let's go a little lower.
いいよ、じゃあちょっと下も
Do your best.
ちょっと 頑張れ
Wow, nice.
うわ、いいね
It's beautiful.
きれいだね
Is it pretty?
きれいですか?
Super beautiful.
超きれい
I looked back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてみたよ
oh.
おー
Wind belt.
風帯
Hey, just leave it like this, just take a moment to see what's going on.
ちょっとさ、このままさ、 ちょっと映る場合になってごらん
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Well then, put it on.
じゃあ、付け出して
Oh, you have a nice butt.
あ、いいお尻してる
Sure, it's kind of like, yeah, right here, right?
確かに、なんか、 そうだね、ここでしょ?
It fits here.
ここが合ってる
This line is amazing.
これすごいね、ここのライン
Isn't this painful?
これ苦しくないんだ?
It's not painful.
苦しくないです
This is quite difficult, it's not like this.
これなかなかさ、 こういう、こうないよ
Is your butt this color?
お尻がこういう色くるんか
This will be adjusted.
調調されるね、これ
Nice ass.
いいお尻
surely.
確かに
Okay, come over here.
ちょっといいよ、こっち向いて
nice.
いいね
Take a seat.
座ってごらん
oh
お
ー.
ー
No, it's beautiful.
いや、 きれい
Isn't it beautiful?
きれいどうじゃん
I've never been taken like that.
そんな取られることない
It's black.
お黒だ
river
かわ
good.
いい
delicious.
おい しい
It's delicious.
おいしいね
Looks embarrassing.
恥ずかしそう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
amazing.
すごい
There are stains.
シミが
The stains are terrible.
シミがすごい
It's spreading, isn't it?
広がってるよね
I'm getting wet.
濡れてきちゃったの
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
It's turning into a robot.
ロボになってるよ
Your legs are long.
足長いね
My legs are long.
足長いです
Hey.
ねぇ
Looks like Mr. Drill.
ドリルさんみたい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Hey, use your hand to open it.
ちょっとさ、利用手でさ、 開いてさ、
The pussy.
まんこのさ
amazing.
すごい
delicious.
おいしい
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
tree
き
spirit.
れ い
Come on, get in the middle of the bed,
ちょっとさ、ベッドの真ん中入って、
Be quiet.
静寂して
The way you touch it.
触り方はね
How to touch.
触り方
Then it feels good.
そうしたら、 気持ちいい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing, bottom.
すごいね、下
I don't have to try hard.
頑張らなくて
Hey.
ねぇ
Hey, just lick your dick.
ちょっとさ、 チクビをさ、 舐めてこれ
Erotic.
エロ
Yeah, great.
うん、やば
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's dangerous though.
危ないんだけど
Good.
よいしょ
So cute.
かわいいな
dangerous.
危ない
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
It looked like it was going to explode.
爆発しそうだった
No.
ダメだよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hard?
硬め?
It's tough here, isn't it?
硬いんですよね、ここ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Hey, can I put my dick in there?
ちょっとさ、 チンチン入れていい?
May I?
いいですか?
That's fine.
いいですよ
It's tough.
きついね
It's very tight.
すごくきつい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh no, I feel good too.
や ばい、俺も気持ちいいんだけど
I can't move.
動けない
It's really tight.
すごい締まりいいね
amazing.
すごい
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Wait a minute, that's really tough.
ちょっと待って、 すごいきついね
It's really tight.
すごいきつい
すごい きつい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's really tight.
すごい きつい
I can't move.
動けない
My back can get tired.
腰疲れできるの
It's really tight.
すごい締まるね
That's amazing.
すごいわ
This is dangerous.
危ないね、これ
I got my hands on it and moved it.
手ついてさ、 動かしたって
Put your foot in slowly.
ゆっくり足入れして
amazing.
すごい
Good job, it's tough.
やるのいいね、きつい
It's heavy.
重いね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's good to do it.
やるのいいね
I'll take it out in a moment.
ちょっともう、出しちゃうよ
I'll bring it out again.
もう一回に出しちゃうよ
I was so wet.
すごいびしょびしょやっちゃった